Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Subject Files, 6
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files, 13
    - Nerken, Albert – Nerken Center, 1989 November-1990 May; 530 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Nespoli, Paolo A., 1985 July-1988 November; 531 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Newell, James F., 1991 August-September; 532 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Newman, Joseph H., 1979 December-1987 September; 533 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - New Orleans – National Trustee Workshop, 1983 August-October; 534 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - SUNY New Paltz, 1984 April-June; 535 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Newsday, 1978 October-1985 Febraury; 536 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Newsweek – Letter to the Editor, 1994 August; 537 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - New York Academy of Science, 1987 July-October; 538 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - New York City Partnership – New York: How to Get To The 21st Century, 1984; 539 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - New York City Technical Assistance Center, 1992-1993; 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1990 March; 540 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - New York State Commission on Science & Technology, 1987 March; 541 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1987 March-October; 542 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1987 February-April; 543 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - New York Telephone, 1987 June-December; 544 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - New York University, 1983 June-1989 October; 545 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Nichols, Alan, 1978 February-1989 October; 546 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Nielsen, John, 1976 March-1989 August; 547 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Nishijima, Yasunori, 1986 December-1990 April; 548 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - N-Nat – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1978-1990; 549 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Nau-New – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1982-1990; 550 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - New York – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990; 551 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Nic-Nix – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1978-1989; 552 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Oakland University – Speech, November 13, 1984, 1984 July-1985 January; 553 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Oakland University – Speech, November 13, 1984 – Notes, Undated; 554 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Organisation De Cooperation et de Developpement Economiques (OECD), Undated; 555 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1970 January-1983 January; 557 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1983 February-1984 May; 558 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1984 June-1990 September; 559 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1991 June-1992; 560 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1990 October-1991 March; 562 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal – Publications, Undated; 561 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - O.E.C.D - Portugal - Oversize, 1990 October 3; 973 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Othmer, Donald, 1993 October, 1994 September; 563 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Ottawa Symposium, 1974-1975; 564 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Ottawa Symposium, 1976 March-1991 January, Undated; 565 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Paley, Henry, 1973 October-1975 November; 566 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Palm Springs, California – Higher Education Executive Conference, 1990 February-March; 567 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Papadakis, Constantine N., 1993 April; 568 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic University– Executive Committee Notes, Undated; 569 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic University – Protocol, 1985 September-1988 June; 570 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic University - Question & Answer Brochure, 1988 September-October; 571 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic University – Telephone Directory, 1992, 1994; 572 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Pond, Jules, 1952, 1974 October-1981 March; 573 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Proskaver, Dr. Eric, 1988 September; 574 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Pusey, Nathan Marsh, 1974 December-1975 December; 575 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Radley, Melanie L., 1985 June-December; 576 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Reiss Romoli, 1989 June-1990 December; 577 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Reliance Award for Excellence in Education, 1991 June; 578 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Reza, Ambassador Fazlollah, 1967 August-1976 May; 579 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Romanelli, Otto - RESTRICT, 1993 June-August; 580 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco – Polytechnic Creative Technology Award Dinner, 1990 June-1991 February; 581 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Savage, Marcia A., 1993 January-February; 582 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Schillinger, Professor A. George, 1979 December-1991 October, Undated; 584 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Schriesheim, Robert, 1992 November 12; 585 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Schwabacher, Sara, 1991 June; 587 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Schwartz, Gail G., 1986 January-March; 586 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Schwartz, Samuel I., 1990 July; 4550 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Senior Management Meeting – October 16, 1989, 1988 August-1989 October; 588 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Center for Services Information Systems Research, 1988 January; 589 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Settle, Thomas B.- 1989, 1993, 1987 March, 1990 May; 590 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Sforza, Pasquale M., 1974 August-1988 December; 591 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Sherbourne, Dr. Archibald Norbert, 1982 November-1989 January; 592 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Sie, John, 1986-1989 March; 593 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Sigma Xi, 1993 October; 594 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Sih, George, 1992 November-December; 595 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Silha, Otta, 1991 January-1992 November; 596 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Silleck, Clarence F., 1970 February-1993 January; 597 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Simmonds, Geoffrey, 1986 September-December; 598 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Slides – George Bugliarello – Miscellaneous, Undated; 599 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Floyd - RESTRICT, 1988 November; 600 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Karl, 1981 December-1986; 601 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Social Technology – Research & notes, 1965 February-1976 June; 602 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Social Technology – Research & notes, 1976 July-1979 August; 603 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Social Technology – Research & notes, Undated; 604 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Association Sophia Antipolis, 1981 - 1984 July; 605 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Association Sophia Antipolis, 1984 October-1986 December; 606 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sophia International Management Centre, 1991 August; 607 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sorghum Beer, South Africa, 1993 December; 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Spencer, William (Xerox) – May 13, 1987 visit, 1987 May-1990 October; 608 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Sperry, 1986 May; 609 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Spruck, Albert E., 1962 March-1971 March; 610 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Spruck, Albert E., 1971 June–1976 April; 611 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Steingut, Stanley, 1971 October-1989 June; 612 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Stockholm – University-Industry Research Interactions, 1982 October-1983 November; 613 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Stockholm – University-Industry Research Interactions - Notes, 1983 December-1984 January; 614 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Strang, Charles, 1977 September-1990 January; 615 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Polytechnic University - Strategic Plan, 1992 September-November; 616 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Strauss, Dr. Jon C., 1988 March-1990 February; 617 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Strom, Margaret A., 1986 August-1987 February; 618 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Stroud, W.G., 1989 January-1990 June; 619 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Student Center, 1978 October-1979 October; 620 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Sudarsky, Jerry, 1976 February-1993 February; 621 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Sudensky, Leon- RESTRICT, 1993 May; 622 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Summer, Eric E., 1989 July-November; 623 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - SUNY Farmingdale, 1984 December-1990 March; 624 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Swanson, Elston H., 1977 July-1987 March; 625 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Swartz, Jerome, 1987 August-1990 March; 626 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Sweeney, Richard, 1984 May-1987 August; 627 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Szeglin, Arthur R., 1987 March, 1990 May; 4551 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Szyliowicz, Joseph S., 1986 March-July; 628 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Sci-St – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1977-1990; 629 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Sub-Sy – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 630 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Taiwan, China – Pacific Rim Conference on the Resource Management, 1990 August-1993 May; 631 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Taiwan, China – GB Trip, 1978 September-1980 February; 632 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Taiwan, China – Miscellaneous, 1974 July-1979; 633 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Technology in Society, 1974 February-1990 November; 634 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic University - Ten Year Plan, 1986 March; 635 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Tamir, Theodor, 1974 December-1977 February, 1992 March; 636 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Tedesko, Dr. Anton, 1989 March-1990 April; 637 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Tilghman, James W., 1991 August-September; 638 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic University - Time Reports, 1990 March-1992 November; 639 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Tiribelli, Claudio, 1986 October-1991 January, Undated; 640 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tisch, Preston Robert, 1985 March-1990 August; 649 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tobias, Abraham Joel, 1988 February-1990 June; 648 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Tobin, John P. Jr., 1989 July-1990 January; 647 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Tooney, Nancy M., 1985 August-1988 December; 646 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Torda, T. Paul, 1975 July-1988 February; 641 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Townsend, Alair A., 1985 May-1990 July; 645 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Townsend, Paul, 1974 November-1980 June; 644 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel, 1990 April-May; 643 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - John Trani M. – General Electric, 1986 September-1993 June; 642 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Tribus, Myron, 1988 January-September; 658 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Trump, John George, 1975 August-1985 September; 657 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - TRW Defense Systems Group, 1988 August; 4552 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Tsinghua University, 1985 January-June; 656 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Tuck, Eugene, 1988 June-1990 May; 655 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Tucker, Joan K., 1989 September-1990 June; 654 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Tung Au, Dr. Stephen, 1985 December-1986 September; 653 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Turkey, 1987 July-1990 March; 652 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Turkstra, Dr. Carl, 1985 February-1988 June; 651 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - TWA, 1980 November-1986 August; 650 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Th-Tr – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 659 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Tr-Ty – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 660 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Ubertini, Ing. Lucio, 1988 October-1989 November; 661 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Udine, Italy – Speech, August 21-31 1983, 1983 May-August; 662 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Udry, William R., 1985 May-1989 December; 663 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Union Carbide Corporation, 1975 July-1976 October; 664 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - United Engineering Trustees, 1976 October, 1985 May; 665 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - U.N.E.S.C.O., 1976 June-August; 666 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - U.N.I.D.O. (United Nations Industrial Development Organization), 1982 April, 1995 November; 667 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - United Nations University, 1974 January-1980 November; 668 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Department of Education, 1985 December, 1987 July; 669 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1988 April; 670 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1987; 671 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - United States Steel Foundation, 1987 January-September; 672 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - United Technologies, 1976 February-1988 February; 673 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - United Way, 1987 September-1990 September, Undated; 674 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - University of Minnesota, 1983 April-1984 February; 676 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - University Research Center, 1974 October-November, 1987 July; 675 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Unny, Professor T.E., 1976 November, 1977 June; 677 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Untapped Resources Inc., 1989 May; 678 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Upward Bound, 1971 April, 1973 December; 679 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Utica, New York - Conference, 1985 October 30; 680 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Utsumi, Takeshi, 1987 July-October; 681 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Uen-United States - Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990; 682 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Universidad – United States – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 683 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Valencia, 1989 December-1990 January; 689 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Van Nostrand, W.J., 1977 January-March; 688 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Van Slyke, Richard, 1981 November-1989 April; 687 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Vellam, Diego, 1986 February-April; 686 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Venice, Italy – International Conference, 1986 February-1987 November; 685 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Verga, Richard, 1986 September-1989 June; 684 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Vicario, Emilio C.O., 1987 April-1989 November; 696 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Vickers, Dr. Clinton J., 1987 February-1989 September; 695 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Vigilante, Frank S., 1985 October-1987 April; 694 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Viola, Giulio, 1986 October, 1990 June; 693 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1979 January, 1988 February; 692 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Vitagliano, Vincent J., 1977 August, 1987 February; 691 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Vitrogan, David, 1988 December-1989 February; 690 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Vac-Ver – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 697 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Ves-Vou – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 698 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Wakstein, Dr. Charles, 1984 March-1985 November; 699 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Walker, David, 1989 February-1990 May; 700 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Walker, John A.S., 1987 January-July; 701 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Wallach, Steven J., 1987 January–1990 May; 702 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Walsh, Patrick J., 1985 December-1986 January; 703 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Wandmacher, Dean Cornelius, 1986 July-1990 April; 704 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Wang, Dr. An, 1982 January-December; 705 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Wang, Frank, 1988 March-April; 706 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Waring, John A., 1991; 707 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Watkins, James D., 1989 September-December; 708 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Watt, Dr. Brian J., 1989 November-1990 August; 709 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - We Care About New York, Inc., 1982 September-1989 December; 710 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Wechsler, Dr. Harry C., 1981 January-1990 March; 711 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Weinig, Sheldon, 1979 March-1990 June; 712 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Weiss, Dr. Charles, 1987 September-1990 May; 713 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Weiss, Eric A., 1987 October-1989 May; 714 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Welcome Back to Brooklyn, 1985 November-1990 June; 715 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Weldes, Helmut H., 1984 April; 716 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Wenk, Edward Jr., 1979 September-1983 January; 717 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Wenners, Colonel Edward B., 1986 April-1987 May; 718 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Westchester Advisory Board, 1985 February-1989 December; 719 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Westinghouse Educational Foundation, 1975 October-1990 February; 720 (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1976 January-1988 April; 721 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Westway, 1981 March-1984 January; 722 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Whang, Sung H., 1987 March-1989 September; 729 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Wheeler, Harold A., 1985 January-1990 February; 723 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - White, Dr. George R., 1985 March-June; 728 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - White, Dr. Robert, 1979 October-1989 February; 727 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Whitehead, John (Jack) C., 1983 April-July; 726 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Whitley, Arthur F., 1980 October, 1984 March; 725 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Who's Who in America, 1986-1990; 724 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wilkowski, Ambassador Jean, 1983 June-August; 735 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - William, W. John, 1975 September-1977 February; 733 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Arthur F., 1989 July-October; 734 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Willnus, Harry G., 1954 May-1968 April; 732 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Wishnik, William, 1981 September-1987 March; 731 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Wistar Institute, 1989 July-August; 730 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Wojick, David E., 1975 November-1988 January; 736 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Women on the Job, 1986 March-September; 4553 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Women's Issues, 1986 November-1988 June; 737 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Wouk, Dr. Victor, 1988 April; 738 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Wunsch, Eric M., 1982 June-1989 December; 739 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Wad-Way– Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 740 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - We-West – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1976-1989; 741 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Wha-Wilc – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990; 742 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Wild-Witt – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 743 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - WNET-Wy – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990; 744 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - X – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1984, 1988; 745 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Yanizeski, Dr. George M., 1979 September-1988 January; 746 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Yarmouk University, 1978 June-1979 January; 747 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Yearbook, 1985-1990 February; 750 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Federal University of Technology, Yola (Nigeria), 1982 March-May; 748 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Youth in Engineering & Science (YES), 1987 October-1990 May; 749 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Yac-You-Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1980-1988; 751 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Zandi, Iraj, 1985 November; 4554 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Zelazny, Michele, 1988 July-August; 752 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Zeldin, Yevgeny, 1983 December-October; 753 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Zesigner, Judith C., 1988 June-August; 754 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Zheng, Dr. Wanlie, 1984 April-July; 755 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Zoppi, Sergio, 1984 July-1985 October; 756 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Za-Zuck - Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990; 4555 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Subseries B: MetroTech Center, 14
    Historical Note
    Metropolitan Technology Center (MetroTech Center) is a 16 acre, 4.7 million square foot urban knowledge park. A knowledge park is an environment that combines an industry and a knowledge institute focused on science and technology, in this case Polytechnic Institute. George Bugliarello, "The Father of MetroTech," worked in collaboration with New York City officials, including Mayor Ed Koch and Borough President Howard Golden, and private commercial real estate developer Bruce Ratner in order to entice commercial businesses to relocate to downtown Brooklyn to be part of MetroTech. The concept for the MetroTech Center was first proposed by George Bugliarello to the Polytechnic Board in 1975. Construction began on MetroTech in 1989. Bern Dibner Library for Science & Technology was the first Polytechnic building completed at MetroTech in 1992. The final building, 12 MetroTech, was completed in 2004.
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 January; 1143 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 February; 1144 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 March; 1145 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 April; 1146 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 May; 1147 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 June; 1148 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 July; 1149 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 August; 1150 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 September; 1151 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 October; 1152 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 November; 1153 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1992 December; 1154 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 April; 1155 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 May; 1156 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 June; 1157 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 July; 1158 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 August; 1159 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Gayla Merryman, 1993 September; 1160 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Appointment Books – Secretary's Book of Gayla & SYS Meetings, 1986; 1161 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Appointment Books – R.J.M., 1986; 1162 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Appointment Books – Susan, 1985; 1163 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Appointment Books, 1985; 1164 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Appointment Books – Sy, 1985; 1165 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Appointment Books - Gayla Merryman, 1985; 1166 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher (SS), 1984; 1167 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Appointment Books – 2, 1984; 1168 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher, 1988; 1169 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher, 1987; 1170 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Books – SS, 1987; 1171 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Books – RJM, 1987; 1172 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1987; 1173 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1986; 1174 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Books, 1985-1986; 1175 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher, 1986; 1176 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1990; 1177 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher, 1990; 1178 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Appointment Books – SS & GVM, 1990; 1179 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Appointment Books – SS & GVM, 1989; 1180 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Appointment Books – Seymour Scher, 1989; 1181 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1989; 1182 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Appointment Books - Gayla Merryman, 1988; 4556 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Appointment Books – SS & GVM, 1988; 1183 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1993; 1184 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1992; 1185 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Appointment Books – Gayla Merryman, 1991; 1186 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Brochures – Ordering, Drafts – 1, 1983-1984; 1187 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Brochures – Ordering, Drafts – 2, 1983-1984; 1188 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Brochures – Ordering, Drafts – 3, 1983-1984; 1189 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Roger, Sheldon, 1982-1983; 1190 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - News Clippings – M.T.C. – 1, 1981-1982; 1191 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - News Clippings – M.T.C. – 2, 1981-1982; 1192 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - New York City Public Development Corporation (N.Y.C.P.D.C.) - 1, 1984 January-October; 1193 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - N.Y.C.P.D.C. – 2, 1984 March-May; 1194 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - N.Y.C.P.D.C. - 3, 1984; 4557 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Shearson / American Express, 1982-1985; 1195 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Research & Development 1 (#1) Grant for Developing Research and Development firms in downtown Brooklyn – Grant Proposals (Drafts, Correspondence, Etc.), 1979-1980; 1196 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Research & Development 1 (#2) Grant Proposals, 1980; 1197 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Research & Development 1 (#3) Grant Dispersal, Research - 1, 1981; 1198 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Research & Development 1 (#4) Grant Dispersal, Research – 2, 1981; 1199 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Research & Development 1 (#5) Final Grant Report, Extension, Etc., 1981; 1200 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Research & Development 1 (#6) Grant, 1982; 1201 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Research & Development 1 – Natkins – Consultant, 1981; 1202 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Research & Development 1 – Payroll Allocation, 1980-1982; 1203 (Box 17, Folder 6)